Infinite Company STAPLA - 69 employees.
A total of 69 STAPLA members are making the most of their diverse personalities and entertainment skills as employees.
This is a project that aims to solve the problems of business organisations and shops, and to energise and enliven the whole of Japan.
If you have something you are confident about, we would like you to promote it.
We'd like you to promote something that you have confidence in.
I'm Nami Tsujinaka, known as Cho-TokiMeki Propaganda.
The members of Chotokisen are all
We all love make-up and fashion.
We have a lot of female fans and young fans.
We have a lot of fans, so we'd like to do work that makes the most of our friends and get the word out.
I want you to do it.
The fan representative said...
Okay, Harima.
Hi, I'm Kana Harima from Namie Girls' First Union.
I'm a member of the Namiye Girls' First Union.
We are working on the concept of spreading smiles not only in the town of Namie, but all over the country.
We are working based on the concept of spreading smiles not only in Namiye Town, but all over the country.
We go to all parts of the country to eat delicious food, see the scenery, and meet people who live there.
to see delicious food and scenery, and to interact with the people who live there.
and the people who live there.
I would like to deepen the exchange between people who live in each area and people who live there.
I would like to share the good qualities of the local area.
Through the activities of the Namie Women's Association
I would like to spread the good qualities of the area through the activities of the Namie Girls' First Association.
We also have Ayaka Sasaki as a member.
is also a member of our group.
I am also a member of this Namie Girls' First Association.
I'm also a member of Namie Girl's First Association, so I'm a bit fresh and young.
I'd like to go to various places with everyone.
I'm half of the members, and half of the members are myself.
I also want to eat food from all over the country.
Ebitu-chan.
Is it okay if it's personal?
Yes, that's fine.
Well, I personally love saunas.
I love saunas, and I love saunas in Staples.
I love saunas.
There's a lot of them.
There are a lot of them.
That's why we can cross the boundaries of the group.
We can do PR just for sauna lovers.
I'd like to have saunas all over the country.
I think it would be great if we could do something like that.
Everyone in Ebitu has their own hobbies.
I'm Karen Tachibana from Ikinari Talk.
It's very cold in Tohoku.
We've been living in the extreme cold everyday.
It's that cold.
Yes, we have confidence in our endurance.
There is spring and summer, too, right?
Yes, yes, we are confident in our perseverance in everything, even in spring and summer.
I believe that you can survive if you have patience in everything.
I'm here to show you how patient I am.
I'm a CCO.
CCO.
As Chief Cold Officer, I'll do my best.
I see, so it's C for cold.
That's right.
So you'll be doing some physical, cold location work?
Yes, I'll take care of that.
That's great.
I'm Norina Haruno of the Batten Girls' Choir.
We're based in Kyushu.
And all the members are from Kyushu.
We're the go-to people for all things Kyushu.
Because we live in Kyushu
We pride ourselves on being the most mobile idols
We go wherever we go.
If you have any jobs that make use of our travel distance, we'd love to hear from you!
We look forward to working with you.
I'm Ira from Ameflasi.
We members of Amefrasi like to eat a lot.
We can enjoy all kinds of food, so we're looking forward to working with you in the food industry.
We're looking forward to working with you in the food industry.
Ramen.
I really love ramen.
I used to make instant ramen at night and eat it alone.
I used to do that a lot.
So ramen is my strongest area.
I really want to work with ramen.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm Akimoto from Team Shachi.
We are the first team in Nagoya and the first team in Aichi Prefecture.
We've also been Nagoya's tourism ambassadors for the past eight years.
We have actually collaborated with various local companies.
We have collaborated with many local companies, so you can trust Team Shachi with your Nagoya work.
And since our group concept is "Super Tough", we are always looking for new ideas and ideas.
We are looking forward to working with Team Shachi for your physical work.
All of our members love the sea.
We have scuba diving licenses
We have a licence to ride a sea bike on the water, and we have a fisherman.
And we also have a fisherman.
Sea fishing.
Not fishing, all the time.
I go sea fishing once or twice a month.
I even handle the fish.
I'd love to work in the sea.
Yellowtail?
I catch yellowtails and other fish, process them myself, and eat them.
I'm looking forward to working with you in the fishing industry.
We look forward to working with you.
Here you go.
Yes, I'm Ibuki Sanda from Crown Pop. I'm Sanda Ibuki of Crown Pop.
We, Crown Pop, were originally formed by people with dance experience,
So we have a high level of athletic ability.
We also have experience as exclusive models,
They actually edit their own videos and use them in their live performances.
We also have girls with great creative abilities.
We dare to say that our group colour is
No, no, no, sorry.
We don't dare to make a member colour.
Our group colour is blue.
Yes, I am the director of the Ugqa Village Star. I look forward to working with you.
Yes, the concept of the Ucka group is called Resounding Youth Novels,
We often use travel as a theme in our activities,
I would like to visit the actual places where the novels are set and give you some recommendations for food and other things to eat.
I would be happy if I could tell you about the scenery of the town.
I'd be very happy to tell you about it!
We are currently holding a spring tour.
The concept of the spring tour is a journey.
I would love to visit various places and
Delicious food
I would like to tell you about the fun and games of the place
I hope we can share these things with you.
Thank you very much.
I'm Ruri Shiraishi, a STAPLARA research student.
There are 12 of us in the STAPLAR research students.
The youngest is in sixth grade.
The oldest is a senior in high school.
We're a very young group with a great age range.
We want to challenge ourselves in many different ways.
We're looking forward to all kinds of jobs.
That's one of the reasons.
I also have a personal interest in this.
I'm from Shizuoka and I love tea.
I'm also looking forward to working in the tea industry.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm glad you have a rival, and I'm glad there's another girl from the same background.
We'll work hard together.
If there's anything you'd like to do, please take this opportunity to raise your hand.
Raise your hands, please.
My name is Nao Sakura from Team Orca.
I really love rice.
I have a reputation among the members for having big bites.
I'm looking forward to working with rice.
I look forward to working with you.
Rice?
White rice.
Yes, I especially love the rice from Gifu, near my home town.
I eat a lot of it at home.
I see.
You love white rice, Nao!
In a company, it's important to have the will to do what you want to do, isn't it?
You have to appeal to people.
I'm Yu Watanabe, a STAPLA research student.
Actually, I love games.
I love games so much that I even include them in my self-evaluation.
I'd love to work in anything related to games.
I'm open to anything, as long as it's game-related.
I'm looking forward to all kinds of game-related work.
Thank you, I'm Suda Hiko from the Super Exciting Propaganda Department, and I'm looking forward to working on anything game-related.
I'm Sodaki from the Kesende Department. I have a dog.
We all love animals, so I'd be happy to work with animals.
I'd be very happy to work with animals.
It's true, but I'm sure there are lots of other members who have pets.
I'm from Kazamino Junior High School in Emishi.
I love shoujo manga, and even now I read about eight of them on a manga app at the same time.
I still read about eight at the same time on a manga app, so I think I'm a bit limited.
I'd appreciate it if you could give me a job in shoujo manga.
I'm Awairuri from Ukka and I love sweets.
I like gummy bears so much that I eat them every day and carry them around with me.
I like them so much that I think my body is made of them.
I would be very happy if I could get a job working with gummy bears.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
My name is Saho Tanaka from Crown Pop.
I'm good at sewing and I'm so good with my hands that I even made my own nativity costumes.
If there is a job where I can make use of my dexterity, or if there is a job related to fabric or sewing, please leave it to me!
I look forward to working with you!
Amazing!
Yes, I'm Yuna Hazuki, suddenly from Tohoku.
I love drinking sake, and last time I went to a sake brewery in Kawagoe with Shurin as part of this No Rules collaboration. I think my liver is strong, so please let me drink as much as I want.
Also...
Suddenly, we're from Tohoku!
We are all from Tohoku.
We all live in a house with a garden.
I think it's something unique to Tohoku.
So I'd love to work for a house builder.
If you have any house-related jobs...
I'm sure you'll be able to find a garden or a parking lot at Tohoku.
You have a parking lot, right?
Or a child who has a field.
Or a rice paddy?
or a strawberry field...
It's really unique to Tohoku!
And some have boats.
I would be very happy if we could collaborate on something that is unique to Tohoku.
I'd be very happy to collaborate with them.
When there are so many people, there's a lot of individuality.
I thought it would be great to have 10 people in Toiro.
I thought it would be great if we could work together as 10 people in a group.
I hope we can do something that crosses the boundaries of the group.
I didn't know that Sahorn made the treasure himself.
I didn't know that everyone in Tohoku has a lot of land like that.
It was a new discovery for us.
I don't think I have to tell you...
I think my cuteness is my best feature.
I'm looking forward to working with you to show off my cuteness.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
Lastly, she also gave a good PR speech about herself.
This is Ayaka Sasaki.
Not one of you could say that you're cute...
I don't think I'm the only one who's cute.
I'm sorry, I thought I was the only one who could do it.
Everyone's just being modest.
We've just started up today.
Are you ready to pull it all together?
That's great.
That's a lot of responsibility.
Take it back to the car.
This is the car, this is the car, this is the car, this is the car, this is the car, this is the car, this is the car, this is the car.
This is the car.
Which car do you take it back to?
Just, you know... take it to different places.
You know, we're all just having fun together.
Have fun and be merry.
I'd like to walk a little further.